It appeared as if humanity will soon
be destroyed by the demons.
But there was a mage who fought alone
and saved everyone.
He was called the Magic Emperor
and became a legend.
This is the Black Market.
This place is a little dangerous.
but it has great magic tools
that are super effective.
Damn it! I lost again.
That's because I can see the future.
That old lady is really good.
Anyway. it's not the time for this now.
She's so cute!
The Black Market doesn't seem
like a place for pretty girls like you.
Get lost. you flying insect.
Hey! I found an interesting item!
This little brat...
Wait. Aren't you Haha?
I'm Sekke! Not Haha!
Haha. how have you been?
I told you! I'm Haha...
No. I mean. Sekke!
Who is he?
Someone I met at the entrance exam.
I see. He's a member of the Green Mantis.
Are these two pretty ladies with him?
If so.
these two must be members
of the Black Bull.
Asta. you bastard.
Despite being in the Black Bull.
you're making me jealous.
Come to think of it.
it's all your fault that I ended up
in the Green Mantis.
How infuriating.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
You're out shopping with the girls?
Well. since today's our day off.
You sure know how to have a good time.
Even if it's your day off.
instead of messing around.
don't you think it's better to do
some odd jobs and earn some points?
I heard that the Black Bull
have negative stars.
Stars!
That's right! Listen to this!
I got a star from the Magic Emperor
on my first mission!
What? You must be kidding!
Well. both of them did a very good job.
They're serious?
No. I should calm down.
I see! Seems like you're working hard.
What about you. Haha?
It's Sekke!
Just the other day.
I got my second star...
No. potato.
Thief!
My winning prize!
Stop right there!
It's that old lady.
He's sure got some nerve
to steal in front of Magic Knights.
Indeed.
I'm sure we can just leave it to that kid.
I'm counting on you.
I'm not going to let you
take all the limelight. Asta!
Bronze Creation Magic.
Sekke's Shooting Star!
-Lame!
-Gross!
Leave this to me.
You lovely ladies and that old lady
can just sit back and wait.
-So dirty!
-No!
Stop right there!
Try and catch me if you can.
Stop there!
Stop!
Yes?
I'm sorry!
I finally got rid of him.
It's not over yet!
He's so persistent!
I can't see!
I won't let you get away!
How is he catching up with me
when he's only running?
This is not going to end
if I don't do something about that cloud.
If it's a cloud created by magic...
Okay!
Do you seriously think you can
cut through my Bandit's Cloud Wind--
What?
You're not getting away!
Haha?
I'm taking the credit!
That is so cool!
You're under arrest!
The credit is all mine!
That's...
Stop laughing! It's annoying!
I'm taking you down with me.
What's wrong. Haha?
Poison.
The poison's coursing through my body.
Hang in there. Haha!
Am I going to die?
Now that I think about it. I was once...
trying to get to the top too.
Haha!
Should I entrust it to him?
You're the man who defeated me.
Make it all the way to the top
for my sake too.
I'm entrusting
my dream to you!
Haha.
I guess having an ending like this
isn't so bad.
Haha?
Haha!
What?
I'm not dead.
What are you doing?
Don't entrust something
so important to anyone so easily!
Survive and make your own dream come true!
Don't give up. you idiot!
Jeez. there's no way
you would die from this.
It's just some temporary irritant poison.
Apply this Shique ointment
and you'll be better in no time.
Keep improving yourself
until the next time we meet. Asta!
See you!
See you. Haha!
Little Boy may look younger
than him on the outside.
but he's definitely stronger
on the inside.
Don't let it get taken again. Granny.
Thank you. Magic Knights.
See you. Granny.
Be careful.
May you live a long life.
Nullification of magic?
That's a type of magic
I've never seen before.
Strictly speaking. is that even magic?
Yami sure took in an interesting kid.
This is why I can't stop wandering
around in disguise.
I finally found you!
What are you doing here?
Magic Emperor.
28TH MAGIC EMPEROR. JULIUS NOVACHRONO
What am I doing?
I'm strolling through the castle town.
hoping to come across new magic.
What?
Are you aware of your own position?
Encounters with magic
are once in a lifetime.
That's why I said--
You never know what kind of magic
you're going to encounter or where.
Listen to me. you magic maniac!
Calm down. will you. Marx?
Isn't that the new kid
from William's squad?
Well then.
I'm off to encounter even more new magic.
I'll be right back.
Hold on!
MEMBER OF THE GOLDEN DAWN. KLAUS LUNNETTES
Yuno. Golden Dawn's newbie.
The genius that
every captain of Magic Knights
wanted in their squads.
And Mimosa Vermillion.
a royal who is also a newbie.
Their first mission together
is to act as bodyguards
for Salim Hapshass?
Escorting the son of Lord Hapshass
of the House of Lords.
to our ally. the Heart Kingdom?
You know who Lord Hapshass is. don't you?
I've only heard of his name.
Since he's an upstart noble.
he doesn't quite have a good reputation.
That's why
he's worried that his son.
who's going to study in the Heart Kingdom.
might be targeted by some bandits.
But there are many powerful mages
among his own family.
He feels more reassured to have
the famous Magic Knights
as bodyguards.
Lord Hapshass makes
very generous donations
to the Magic Knights every year.
so as a civil servant.
I couldn't just refuse.
Are you reluctant to do it?
No!
We must fulfill every kind of mission.
This is also for the sake
of the Clover Kingdom.
Yes. I understand.
Take Mimosa with you too.
The three of you. including you
as their mentor. are enough for the job.
I'll leave the newbies to your care.
Salim Hapshass lost to Yuno
in the final round of the Entrance Exam
and ended up being unable
to join the Magic Knights.
So why did he appoint Yuno
to be one of his bodyguards?
It's my first mission and I'm so nervous.
Mr. Klaus. Yuno. it's a pleasure
to work with you.
Yes.
Don't let your guard down. Mimosa.
Yes!
You too.
I know.
What an insolent newbie.
How have you been. Yuno?
Don't make that scary face.
I requested you as my bodyguard
because I wanted to apologize.
Your goal is to become
the Magic Emperor. isn't it?
How did you know?
All of the captains raised their hands.
You could've joined any squad.
and you ended up choosing the Golden Dawn.
so I figured that must be why.
I'm sure you'll do
an outstanding job from now on.
and your name will spread
throughout the entire kingdom.
Everyone will know you
as Yuno of the Clover Grimoire.
Make sure your dream of becoming
the Magic Emperor comes true.
That way. I'll be able to brag
to my future children
that I once fought the Magic Emperor.
And then they'll say.
"Father. you're so cool!"
There's still some distance to go
before we reach the Heart Kingdom.
If you don't mind.
could you tell me about yourself?
I won't force you to
if you don't feel like it.
I'm from Hage Village.
I've heard of it.
It's the most remote village. isn't it?
I think that's where the legend
about the first Magic Emperor
defeating the demons comes from.
It's not just a legend.
In fact. a giant skull of the demon
is still there.
Really?
I was abandoned at the door
of a church when I was young.
I've never seen my parents.
and no one knows who they are.
Though the church was poor.
the priest and sisters there
took care of us well.
-I'm very grateful to them.
-No problems so far.
but there must be someone in the Hapshass
family who can use transportation magic.
Why go through all this trouble?
Not to mention
that we're the only bodyguards.
If they were really worried
about the bandits.
why didn't they hire more bodyguards?
There are too many
questionable points in this mission.
What's that?
Those clouds...
They're a little creepy.
I'll go check them out.
Hey! Don't act on your own!
Stay alert. Mimosa.
Yes!
Yuno!
Protect the ship!
That's what I intend to do.
Take this!
That was impressive!
Those men from earlier
were not after Salim?
Thank you for saving me back there.
You're really good. Yuno.
I didn't even have the chance
to use my God of Lightning Rising Salim.
I'm getting more interested in you now.
That's right.
Why don't you take me
to your village for a visit?
I want to see the place
where you were born and raised.
I want to know what environment
you grew up in that made you so strong.
Lord Salim. that'll result in a detour.
Besides. there could be another attack
on the way like what happened just now.
so we should head straight
for the Heart Kingdom--
Even if there are people
trying to harm me.
you guys will protect me. right?
Well...
Of course we will.
But for nobles to go to the most remote
village of peasants. it's---
It's okay. It'll just be a quick visit.
Yes.
I'm sure Yuno would like to go back
to his hometown after all this time
and meet with everyone
back at the church too. right?
That's not your concern.
Don't be like this.
So that's the demon's skull!
It's massive.
Is that a statue of the first
Magic Emperor on top of its head?
I see.
So where is the church?
There.
Yuno!
Welcome back!
I'm back.
You've grown so much!
I haven't changed.
It's only been two months
since I left the village.
Really? But...
Right. it's your face.
You look more mature now.
What brings you here today?
We're on a mission.
so we came to pay a short visit.
Why must I come
to this most remote village?
Well. hello.
I'm Sister Lily.
I'm Klaus Lunettes
of the honorable Golden Dawn.
led by William Vangeance.
I'm a mentor to the new recruits.
Okay. Mr. Klaus.
Thank you for looking after Yuno.
I've heard about your name
from Yuno's letters.
Letters?
What did you write about me?
Jeez!
I'm Mimosa Vermillion.
I joined the squad
at the same time as Yuno.
Yes. I've heard of you
from the letters too.
I see.
What did you write about me?
She's so beautiful.
I'm Salim Hapshass from Hapshass Village.
son of Lord Hapshass of House of Lords.
and the heir to the Hapshass family.
Please remember my name.
No!
I'm so sorry! I unconsciously...
No. it's all right. Sister Lily.
-Yuno!
-It's Yuno!
How have you been?
Welcome back!
What brings you here. Yuno?
Amazing! That's the robe
of the Golden Dawn.
It's the real thing!
It's Yuno!
Where's Asta?
Where is Asta?
Are you keeping in contact with Asta?
No. I'm not.
Are you staying the night tonight?
You are. right?
Well...
Unfortunately. we're just stopping by.
We have to hurry on our way.
-What?
Don't be like this.
There's no need to be in such a hurry.
We can spare an hour or so. right?
But...
Then I'll prepare some nomotato dishes.
It's the specialty of Hage Village.
Yuno. have some before you go.
You guys should have some too. Come on in.
What a magnificent church.
This is my first time seeing
such a small church.
How cute.
Small?
It's like a playhouse.
What?
Yuno. tell us about the Magic Knights.
Tell us!
Why must I enter
such a filthy little church?
-Petite Clover!
Sekke's Haha Lecture.
We're still doing this?
Of course we are. Asta.
since you haven't mastered
the ways of Haha at all.
Your Shooting Star's so cool!
So you understand its value too!
That front part is especially impressive!
Good! You're starting
to master the ways of Haha!
I see. So this is Haha.
That's right.
Starting today. you're a Haha too.
Men are so stupid.
Yuno. that jerk.
He's just a newbie but he's so insolent.
I'm your senior!
If you don't listen to me.
my glasses are not going to remain silent!
Black Clover. Page 13.
"The Magic Emperor Saw. Continued."
My magic is in never giving up!
Subtitle translation by Zoe Wong
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm